Jesse here. If you're watching this video,
it means you've just booked your Solar Advisory Session.
Now, first and foremost, I want to say congrats.
Because the version of you that one year from now has 2,
has 3, has 5, has potentially 10X'd, their Solar Businesses revenue.
This is the first necessary action you must take to get to that point.
And you've just taken it, so genuinely, congrats.
Now, please come prepared through the call. Make sure you have 45 to 60
minutes blocked off in your calendar. Make sure that you have a desktop,
a laptop, a MacBook, you are not on a phone. Make sure that you
have all basic business information readily available.
Make sure you're in an environment with no distractions, so you can 100% focus,
just so we can both have the most productive conversation.
All right what are we going to talk about on the call? Well,
I'm going to find out what you're actually trying to achieve with this.
What is your goal? Okay, what are you looking to get out of this?
Make sure we're a good fit. I'm going to analyze your business,
show you currently where you are leaking revenue in your funnel.
I'm going to give you clear, actionable steps. What's the highest leverage actions you
can make right now to scale more efficiently. Okay and one more gift that
I'm actually going to give you
is this solar savings calculator software,
which I custom built for all of my client solar businesses.
This has helped personally contribute to multi seven figures of revenue generated.
Now, as I said, this is the white label version.
Your version will be customized to your business, to your business logo,
to your color scheme. It's gonna look extremely professional.
Now, everything you're looking at has been built out intentionally with the pure purpose
of aiding and assisting a buyer through the specific solar sales process.
So they get to the end of the call and the only logical decision
is to go with your solution. All right. Now,
why would I be giving this away for free though? If it's such a
valuable asset, it's added so much revenue to my clients.
Well, number one, 99% of business owners are stingy.
I'm the opposite of that. This is me showing you that from now.
Okay. And also, I'm so confident, I'm so convicted in the effectiveness of my
business. My system, that my framework will bring you results guaranteed that I'm happy
to give you this just as a token to show you number one,
the theory behind what I'm doing. So you can start to understand it.
And number two, so you can see the pure magnitude of what implementing an
effective system can actually achieve for your business.
Okay. Now I'm going to run through everything you're seeing in far more detail
on the call. Please make sure all relevant parties that are actually going to
be affected by your business scaling are attending the call.
If you need anything prior to the call, please reach out to me personally.
Now, aside from that, I look forward to chatting.
Bye bye.